https://www.batterydoctor.net.au/g/2390/privacy-policy.html

Thousands of brand new batteries and related products
Shipping daily across Australia -  General public welcome!
We are open for business!
As an online store we are still processing and delivering orders as usual.
Thank you for your support during this crisis.
OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY
Thank you for visiting the The Battery Doctor website.
Protecting customer privacy is very important to us. Our Online Privacy Statement is available to inform you about our collection and use of personal information so that you can make informed choices about how your own information is collected and used. This Online Privacy Statement reflects the The Battery Doctor policies covering personal information collected at this website on or after the effective date shown above.
We believe that information used responsibly benefits consumers and the economy.
The Battery Doctor strives to better serve our customers by offering goods and services that we believe fit their needs and interests. When identifying an opportunity, The Battery Doctor may use consumer information it has collected in an effort to identify consumers who may be interested in that opportunity. For more than few years, consumers and businesses have relied on The Battery Doctor for safe and reliable service. The relationships we have developed through the years have been established based on mutual trust. Each day we and employees and agents strive to reinforce our commitment to our clients and consumers. Central to that commitment is ensuring that we abide by a set of privacy policies, which are outlined below. These policies guide us in the collection and use of information as well as employee responsibilities in protecting your privacy. We use personal information about consumers only in a manner consistent with these policies.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
The Battery Doctor collects personal information in order to offer or provide goods and services to consumers and our customers. We may obtain this information from a variety of sources:
· Directly from customer applications, questionnaires and other materials submitted to us by customers;
· From transactions in which The Battery Doctor and consumers are involved;
· and
· From a variety of third-party sources, such as our business customers, government repositories, consumer reporting agencies and other financial institutions.
DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
The Battery Doctor does not disclose customer information to third parties. Information collected such as email addresses and delivery addresses are used soley by The Battery Doctor to enable us to operate effectively and provide service to its customers.
WE ARE COMMITTED TO PROTECTING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF PERSONAL CONSUMER INFORMATION.
The Battery Doctor limits access to personal information to those employees of The Battery Doctor and its affiliates who need it to fulfill their business responsibilities.
Employees must adhere to The Battery Doctor privacy policies. Employees violating these policies may be subject to disciplinary action, up to and including dismissal.
Vendors and other outside contractors we engage are subject to our contractual requirements to ensure that sensitive personal information is safeguarded.
WE USE APPROPRIATE SECURITY SAFEGUARDS.
At The Battery Doctor, security is a priority. We employ appropriate measures to protect consumer information against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These may include, among others, encryption, physical access security and other appropriate technologies. The Battery Doctor continually reviews and enhances its security systems, as necessary.
WE MAINTAIN PROCEDURES TO ASSURE THE QUALITY OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND WHERE APPLICABLE, WE WILL INFORM CONSUMERS ABOUT HOW THEY CAN ACCESS THEIR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND MAKE CORRECTIONS, IF NECESSARY.
The Battery Doctor employs appropriate measures to assure the quality of information we collect directly from consumers. Where The Battery Doctor collects information directly from consumers or sources other than our business customers, we permit them, if possible, to dispute or correct any erroneous or out-of-date personally identifiable information. Of course, this correction would not be possible if the information is proprietary to one of our business customers, reflects historical transaction information or if correction would violate the privacy or legal rights of a third party. Where applicable, we abide by laws related to such information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a written request that credibly shows error. We reserve the right to independently verify claims made. To protect your privacy and security, we also will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections. We reserve the right to assess a service charge for providing you any information in connection with your request.
The Battery Doctor WEBSITE IS NOT DIRECTED AT CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13.
Our website is not directed at children under the age of 13 and The Battery Doctor does not collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under the age of 13.
WEBSITE MAY BE LINKED TO OTHER WEBSITES
The Battery Doctor may create links to third party websites. The Battery Doctor is not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by websites that are linked from our website.
If you have any questions or indeed comments about our Online Privacy Statement,or for some reason believe we have not adhered to our statement, please contact us.
We may alter this statement as needed for certain products and services and to abide by local laws or regulations around the world. The Battery Doctor reserves the right to amend or modify this statement from time to time. We urge you to review this statement whenever you visit in order to obtain the most current statement. You may change your choices at any time.
New Products
DIGITECH QM1527 - Bargain Multimeter Data Hold Digital with Auto Backlight$30.00$20.00View...
7.2V 6.7Ah High Capacity Square LiIon Battery with CE180 2.1mm DC Jack
Bike Light battery$115.00$89.00View...
Laptop Battery suitable for HP Notebooks$99.00$79.00View...
Battery for Amazon Kindle 7/8 Generation eBook Reader EBB-58-000083$35.00$29.00View...
UE Boom 2 Bluetooth Speaker battery$49.00$35.00View...
2.4v 3Ah 9021B Cordless Drill Battery$39.00$35.00View...
Makita 7.2v battery replacement for 7000 series$40.00$35.00View...
Bosch 14.4v NiMH 3.0Ah Tool Battery$109.00$99.00View...
Ni-MH version battery for EB1820,
EB1820L,
EB1830H,
EB1830HL,
EB1830X,
EB1833X,
EB18B,$239.00View...
6V / 12V 1.0A 7 Step Fully Automatic Lead Acid Battery Charger ICS1$49.00$45.00View...
Victron 6-35VDC Smart BatteryProtect 12/24V 65A w/Bluetooth BPR065022000$119.00$109.00View...
Victron 24-64VDC Smart BatteryProtect 48V 100A w/Bluetooth BPR110048000$309.00$299.00View...
Victron 6-35VDC Smart BatteryProtect 12/24V 220A w/Bluetooth BPR122022000$236.00$226.00View...
Victron 6-35VDC Smart BatteryProtect 12/24V 100A w/Bluetooth BPR110022000$159.00$149.00View...
Digital and Video Camera Battery suit DSC-HX90
replaces Sony NP-BX1$27.00$20.00View...
23A, GP23A Alkaline Battery Replaces 1811A, 23A, 8F10R, 8LR32, 8LR932, A21, A23, BAT012, E23A, EL12, GP23A, K23A, L1028, LR23A, LRV08, MN21, MN23, MS21, N21, RV08, V23GA, VR22$2.50$2.00View...
Victron Energy 12V 100Ah Sealed Lead Acid Super Cycle Battery (NS70 Size) BAT412110081$415.00$549.00View...
Drypower 12V 75Ah Sealed Lead Acid Gel Deep Cycle Battery$419.00$315.00View...
Samsung C5220 Samsung GT-B3410 Samsung GT-B5310 Samsung GT-C3060 Samsung GT-C5220 Samsung GT-C5510 Samsung GT-M5650 Samsung GT-M7500$29.00$25.00View...
Mobile Phone Battery suitable for Samsung Galaxy S5$39.00$29.00View...
Search
Advanced Search
Members
Please click here to sign in or register.
Order Info.
Images and  information on this website are copyright to Master Instruments Pty Ltd and are used by permission.
Ecommerce Software by Ashop
